[ Watch On KissFlix.co ]
There you are.
How did you start playing?
So creepy.
[Dobby, occupation: freelance host]
Alright, babe, we can continue
where we left off!
"Babe," my ass!
I'm on speakerphone.
There are a lot of customers here.
They might think I'm having an affair.
It's my son, my son.
Okay, I'll stop teasing you.
Let me give you an update.
Tomorrow, there will be someone coming
to check out our dorm.
And if he likes it,
he'll sign the contract.
If there's any update, I'll call you..
But most importantly,
you need to get plenty of rest.
Did you catch a cold?
Your voice is different.
Go to bed early.
Then...
I'll hang up now, babe!
Muah, muah!
Couldn't scold me in time, could you?
Go ahead!
Huh?
There's a safe here?
What's the password?
Is it his birthday?
"Born on February 1, 1951."
Hey!
Why did I suddenly get goosebumps?
Maybe I'm imagining things.
Why this brand, though?
Whoa...
Whoa, whoa.
What's wrong with the lights?
Whoa...
Hey!
Hey!!
My flashlight.
Where's the breaker?
Oh.
Hey, hey.
Come on!
Ow!
Ouch...
Aah, a ghost!
Namo Tassa Bhagavato
Arahato Sammā-Sambuddhassa!
He's still here!
Chinese ghost.
Da cuo te cuo bu yao lai
Wu ru wo de mei
Po zhew lai zhe wa chai wa zho wa
Wo chai eur zhe zhe wo
Da cuo te cuo bu yao lai
Well, I'm a Chinese girlie
I didn't mean to
[Grandpa Danai, occupation: ghost]
[Previous owner of The D Dorm]
[The D Dorm]
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find
what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine,
but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely
when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains,
remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things
await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence
that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings
on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm
is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]
Mr. Dobby,
are you alright?
Mr. Dobby. Hello!
Oh, hello, Mr. Somchai.
Sompong!
Oh, Mr. Sompong!
I didn't sleep very well last night.
I'll take you to
every corner of this dorm.
May I have a moment?
- Yes.
- One second.
Dobby, wake up!
Hello, Mr. Sompong.
- Hello.
- I'll take you to every corner of this building.
If you look at the area as a whole,
it's like we have a male dragon
curled up right here.
Starting from the north!
We have the dragon's head.
The south!
We have the dragon's tail.
And where we're standing!
Right here.
Is the dragon's junk!
That's right.
Hey!
Mr. Sompong!
The dragon's junk is a bit too low.
Its belly button is enough.
The dragon's belly button
is like when the dragon eats something
and gets full,
once it's full, it's prosperous, right?
So if you want to buy this place,
tear it down,
and build a brand-new mall,
mark my words,
it's gonna flourish!
Flourish!
And flourish, Mr. Sompong!
I like the word "flourish."
Then I'll go take another look around.
Of course, Mr. Sompong.
The area on your left
can be turned into a food court.
On the right...
wow, if you tear it all down
and put in high-end brands,
it's going to be marvelous, Mr. Sompong.
I don't really mind the location.
- Yes.
- But I was wondering...
the previous owner of this dorm,
he, uh...
passed away right here.
Seriously, are there ghosts here?
No way!
There definitely aren't any here.
I've lived here and never seen one.
Okay.
Grandpa!
Hey, what are you so scared of?!
[Rooms For Rent, Welcome]
[Danis, occupation: manager of The D Dorm]
Oh!
I'm sorry, Mr. Sompong.
What's wrong with you?!
Why did you bring out
a dead person's photo?!
It's just a sign, isn't it?
I put it at the front
and call customers every day!
Hello.
Are you here to rent a room?
I'm Danis, the manager of this dorm.
Welcome.
I'm not renting.
I want to buy this building.
Then, by all means, get out of here!
We're not selling it!
Hey!
How could you say that to my customer?!
Mr. Sompong, I'll be back soon.
Give me a moment.
Hey, you!
Come talk to me first!
Hey!
Stay here, alright, Gramps?
- What?!
- You.
How could you chase
my customers away like that?!
Whether we sell it or not
is up to his descendants,
not you!
If Gramps had a choice,
he wouldn't leave the dorm to you!
And all this time,
how come you never
took care of your Grandpa?
You left him all alone.
How could you do that?!
Do you even care?!
He just passed away,
and you're selling his property?
Are you crazy?!
He loved this dorm!
I'm gonna pass out...
Are you alright, Miss?
That's refreshing... I'll continue.
You're shameless, outrageous,
brazen, greedy!
Enough!
You're about to say "awful," aren't you?
Huh, how did you know?
You're dissing me
with this much passion,
of course I'd know!
Do you breathe through your gills?
Where I breathe from
is none of your business,
but I won't let this place be sold.
Do you know how much
Gramps loved this place?!
Right, Gramps?
It doesn't matter how much
he loved this dorm!
It's mine now,
and I'll sell it!
Gramps! Gramps, did you hear that?
If you don't want this dorm sold...
Tonight,
come break your ungrateful
grandson's neck!
Sadhu, sadhu!
Put him away!
Not here.
Mr. Sompong might misunderstand!
Gramps, you can hear me, right?
- Uh, Mr. Dobby?
- Yes?
I'll have to bring a Feng Shui Master
to check this place again.
My boss takes this very seriously.
- Uh...
- If we buy a place with a territorial ghost,
- nothing will prosper there.
- Right.
I'll come back later.
- Why not now?
- Don't touch me.
- Mr. Sompong, please!
- I don't believe it!
I'm not listening.
- See you later.
- Mr. Sompong, there are no ghosts here.
- Stop it.
- Mr. Sompong.
You...
Are you a house gecko or something?
- Gramps!
- Come on!
Mr. Sompong.
Hey! Take this with you!
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
Aunite, Auntie.
- Yeah?
- Here's your cooking gas.
Where's the old tank?
Here.
Hey!
[Auntie Duang, occupation: restaurant owner]
I'm not a gas tank!
Are you crazy?
- Then where is it?
- Over there, at the back!
Here.
I saw something short and green,
so I thought you were a gas tank.
Green is an auspicious color.
It helps bring in money, you know?
Wow, short? Sadhu,
I hope your wife is as short as I am!
Oh, Danis! What are you having?
I don't feel like eating, Auntie.
I'm mad at Gramps' grandson.
He plans to sell this building.
He brought someone
to look at our dorm today, too!
Mr. Sompong?
Oh? You know him, too?
A little, yeah.
Mr. Sompong used to work in
the procurement department.
He's looking for a spot to build a mall.
Most importantly,
he's single right now!
He loves pad kra pao
with a runny fried egg. It's his favorite.
But he's not that fun to talk to,
he's quite serious.
Wow! And you say
you only know him a little?
Well...
Well, my mom knows everything.
The only thing she doesn't know
is where her husband has gone.
Oh, wow!
I hear your voice, but where are you?
I'm here!
[Dolly, occupation: stylist]
[Auntie Duang's youngest son]
Hello, Mom.
I almost had a heart attack.
You're a grown-up now,
don't mess around like a kid.
And what are you doing with my curtain?
I'll borrow it for now, Mom.
Look, the pattern is nice.
I still can't find a red-carpet dress
for my customer.
Stop right there.
Your customer's swimsuit is still here.
Oh, come on now, Mom.
They're going to
sell the dorm anyway, aren't they?
I'll buy you new ones
after we finish moving, alright?
No, we're not moving.
A building in a prime location like this
is very hard to find nowadays.
And it's good that I'm here
cause it's near
where your brother is stationed.
[Dollar, occupation: community relations officer]
[Auntie Duang's oldest son]
Dollar, dear,
what happened to your leg?
Well, you made me
pad see ew this morning,
so I ran to burn it off.
There's no need for that.
Hey!
You were so cute with that chubby,
cuddly belly you used to have!
It's not lunch break yet.
Why are you here?
Dolly called me and said
we have to close the shop and move.
Is that true?
No one will have to move away!
I'll protect Gramps' dorm.
I won't allow anyone
to sell this building!
Splendid!
Let me know if you need help.
I'll also help you protect this dorm.
Me too, Mom!
Dollar.
Whatever you and Dolly say,
I'm with you.
No,
I want you to help me change the gas tank.
Ugh...
What's wrong?
The weight is just right.
Can I do one set?
Mm, alright.
Oh, wow...
Mom, wanna try?
No, thanks!
I said I'm going to sell this building!
Why does she need to put this sign here?
You, too.
Why?
[Rooms For Rent, Welcome]
You love this building that much?
Is that why you keep
haunting your descendants?
I've already called an exorcist here.
Just you wait,
and we'll see who prevails.
Hey.
For yin and yang to stay balanced,
humans and ghosts must
not cross paths.
Yin and yang have their flow,
humans and ghosts
must not...
share the same realm!
What are you...
- even doing, huh?!
- Ow!
What the heck, Dobby?
It hurts, you know?
[Dax, occupation: supporting actor]
What are you doing?
Weren't you looking for an exorcist
to drive away your grandpa's ghost?
Mm.
Well, that is me!
I was looking for an exorcist,
not a supporting actor.
It's called a supporting role.
- Most importantly,
- Mm.
I have
been cast as an exorcist
in a Chinese series.
- Which one?
- 'Khemjira: The Kowloon Necropolis Edition.'
The one who showed up for
three seconds before getting killed?
That doesn't count.
Don't you belittle the art of acting.
Although I only appeared for three seconds...
to really get into the role,
I even took an exorcism course.
I got a certificate.
Oh, you got one?!
Here.
Ow! Your certificate is very hard.
- Here, see this?
- Back up a little.
Look.
Whoa, it's real?
You're something else, man.
That's right.
So,
don't you worry.
Today,
I'll perform a ritual
to send your grandpa's ghost
straight back to Shantou!
Good, look at his face there.
He haunts me every night.
I can't get any sleep.
Gramps' ghost?
Is Dobby so deathly afraid of ghosts
that he had to call an exorcist?
♫I can only say I love you so much♫
♫Love you so much♫
♫There's no measure for this love of mine♫
[Daeng the Handyman,
occupation: dorm handyman]
Aren't I cool?
Cool?
My documents are all over the place.
Oh! I'm sorry.
Let me pick them up for you.
Leave them for now.
I need your help. It's urgent.
You know, right?
Gramps' grandson
is going to sell this place!
Huh?!
Daeng, help me think of
a way to stop Gramps' grandson.
Mm...
Why don't we...
just tell him directly?
That we...
love this place
and are very attached to it.
Maybe our sincerity
will reach him,
and we might be able to change his mind!
Ugh! Daeng, there you go
being optimistic again.
Someone like him
wouldn't care about our feelings.
You need a dirty plan
to deal with a dirty person.
Uh...
I don't think dirty things are my forte.
Unlike you.
I think
you'd be better off
consulting my twin brother
about this.
Dum the Guard?
I know it's fitting,
but Dum? Can he really
come up with a dirty plan?
♫I love you more than anyone♫
♫I give my heart to you, my dearest one♫
[Dum the Guard,
occupation: dorm security guard]
That's enough, Dum.
If you don't stop singing,
you're going to lose your job.
Oh...roger that!
I won't sing anymore.
Seriously, are you two really twins?
Your parents didn't adopt one of you
and say that to make you feel better, right?
Don't say that, Ms. Danis!
Why?
Although we look different,
we each have our own charm.
Look at this,
eyes that resemble an eagle's,
a nose that resembles a lion's.
Those lips are definitely a wild gaur's.
Legs that resemble
a Sumatran rhinoceros's.
Ears as grand as an elephant's,
with a tummy as plump
as Po's from Kung Fu Panda!
That's enough.
The more you present me,
the less human I become.
What was that?
I'm a security guard,
not an ambassador for Safari World.
You only mentioned animals.
But...
you're cute to me.
Po!
Do you want some steamed buns?
Ugh! Now that you're here,
help me figure out
how to stop Gramps' grandson
from selling this dorm.
Mm...
I might have a plan.
And that is?
[The D Dorm]
Hey, he might already be here!
Dobby.
Hm?
Stop messing around.
I'm not. You were tapping in rhythm.
It's serious. Sorry.
Great Gods of Heaven and Earth,
celestial generals
and commanders of the five directions,
sacred armies and heavenly steeds...
Here it comes.
Sacred armies and heavenly steeds...
Pass me the sword.
Oh, you're talking to me?
Pasme de talisman.
Here it is again!
Pass me the talisman.
Come on...
Why did you say that with an accent?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Ow! Whoa.
- Hold your sword properly.
- Oh...
- Sorry, sorry.
- Dax.
Grandpa's spirit, reveal yourself!
Dax, quit messing around!
Stop tickling me, then!
Okay, okay, sorry.
Grandpa's spirit, reveal yourself!
Reveal yourself!
Who dares summon me?!
Dax, do you see that?
Grandpa's ghost!
I see him, I see him.
You ungrateful grandson.
Not only do you plan to sell my dorm,
but you also called
an exorcist to challenge me?
Grandpa!
You're the one who started this!
Ghosts should stay with ghosts!
- That's right.
- Why are you bothering me?!
But this is my property!
If you still plan to sell it,
I'll break your neck!
How is it yours?!
It's Mom's now!
- Dax.
- What?
Banish him already!
Shoo...
Go.
Go away!
Go. Shoo.
Hey!
You're shooing a dog, not a ghost.
Shooing a ghost, not a dog.
Dax, didn't you say you studied exorcism?
Do something!
Oh...okay.
Throw it.
Throw it. Do it.
Throw it already. Throw...
Hey!
- Stop shivering already. Just throw it.
- Okay.
Hey, wait.
Hey!
Keep throwing, you losers.
You're not going to hit me anyway.
Stop.
Let me.
You think you're so tough, huh?
See that?
How can a ghost get winded?
Come to think of it...
he wasn't this bloated
the last time I saw him.
Did he drown?
He died on the stairs.
Is he gonna be alright?
No?
That probably hurt.
Give that to me.
- Dobby.
- Huh?
What are you gonna do?
I want to get a closer look.
Let's see.
If this isn't Grandpa's ghost,
I'll beat you until you're skinny.
- I'm screwed!
- Grandpa...
Hey, Dobby, my beloved grandson.
It is
getting late, so I should get some sleep.
I have an errand early tomorrow morning.
Don't sell this dorm yet.
I'll be back soon.
- Bye-bye.
Where are you going?!
Dum, quick! Run!
Go! Hurry!
There's a whole gang here!
Hurry, get them!
Hey, where did they go?
Hey! Where are you going?!
Oh, wow...
- Wait...
- Jeez, you just keep poking me.
This is Grandpa,
not a dead dog.
Grandpa!
Grandpa's ghost...
My beloved grandson, you poor thing.
Dobby!
Stay away, Grandpa!
Where are you going?
Don't follow me!
Why the hell can't I open it?
That is not a doorknob.
Grandpa!
That is my knob...
- Stay away.
- Where are you going?
Why are you running away from me?
- Stay away, Grandpa! I said stay away!
- Let us talk first.
Stop! Stop!
Dobby.
Oh, ghosts should fear talismans.
Take this!
What?
You did not know?
These are all fake talismans.
Here, look at this one.
What does it say?
"I'm too rich. I can't take it anymore."
Maybe whoever wrote this
is a fan of Prime Minister Noo.
You watch the news.
- Talk to me.
- No!
- I need to talk to you.
- No...don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer.
- Stay away.
- Dobby.
Dobby!
Oh, I forgot.
No matter how many times I try,
it does not work.
I cannot touch him.
But Heaven still has mercy on me,
allowing me to communicate with you.
We get to see each other.
Let us talk
when you wake up,
my beloved grandson.
Muah, muah.
[The D Dorm]
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
See how that went?
You dressed up as a ghost to trick him,
but it almost got you sent to jail.
Luckily, Dollar is tight with
the duty officer.
So we were able to settle things
with that Dax guy.
So this is the perk
of having a cop son, huh?
I can rest easy.
He's someone I can count on.
Okay, everyone, dance with me!
Come.
Come on, move with me.
Come on.
He happens to lead
the community aerobics class.
The police catch thieves for a living,
but your son
can only catch the beat.
- One, two, three, four.
- What? Are you mocking me?
You'll have to exercise with me.
Your muscles are all saggy now.
- Mom!
- Don't be stubborn. Come here!
- Go!
But isn't it odd?
Why didn't Dobby
come after us last night?
Could it be that
my little brother's cuteness and chubbiness
made his anger go away?
- No way!
Next time, don't mention my name
unless necessary.
Like I got called in to get scolded.
See?
What do you like about me so much?
Mm...
I don't feel good about this.
Should we...
go get our fortune told?
All of us.
- Let's go, yeah?
- Go get our fortune read?
Go take a shower.
Hey, looking like this,
how could I not shower?
The face paint's about to seep
into my epidermis.
No need for that.
You don't have to shower.
Your skin might get dry.
It's time for work. Your shift has started.
Yeah.
What thief would be scared of me
looking like this?
Let me take a shower.
[D409]
Hey!
Why did you have to sit in the dark?
The light works just fine.
The light works just fine!
The person who turned it on doesn't.
What if our eyes can't adjust in time?!
[Dawin, occupation: tarot reader]
You might make me go blind!
I'm turning on the light, not the sun!
Don't be so dramatic!!
Hey!
Will there ever be a day
when you two meet without arguing?
Let's continue. Sit down!
- Continue.
- Look at our cards first.
Ten of Swords.
It means that this dorm
has come to an end.
- Huh?!
The Tower.
It signifies a sudden change!
As for the Ten of Pentacles,
it guarantees a sale.
Are you implying that
Dobby will sell this dorm
no matter what happens?
So...
is there any other way
to save this dorm, Dawin?
Draw one more card.
Choose wisely.
What does this card mean?
This card is the Hermit.
It can also represent an old man.
Does this mean
Danis needs to find a sponsor?
Like, a rich sugar daddy
who can help buy the dorm from Dobby.
Dolly, there you are.
I turned to teach Grandma
how to twerk for a second,
and you vanished.
- Come on, let's go.
- Mom!
- I can't help you.
- Hurry.
Mom, help...
- I can't.
- Don't help him.
Help yourself. Come.
Or...
Does Danis actually need a sugar daddy?
How convenient.
I've been wanting to take care of someone.
Take care of yourself first.
You're right.
But I won't allow it!
If she actually gets a sugar daddy,
I can't accept that!
Change it. No more "old man."
Can it be a "young man" instead?!
Ugh!
Let him interpret the cards.
We're getting off track.
Mm.
I won't allow it.
So, Dawin?
This card
means that...
an old man will help him change his mind.
I'm sorry,
a fly flew into my mouth.
But that doesn't seem to be the only fly,
since he seems to think
he can fly by deceiving others!
You unhandyman!
How could you say that?
Where are you going?!
Come back, come back!
Calm down. Keep reading.
Why come here just to cause trouble?!
Take it easy.
Are we gonna get anything out of this?
Who grabbed my butt?!
Yeah, what is it, Dax?
I'm at a hotel.
I... I can't stay in the dorm.
Last night,
Grandpa's ghost haunted me.
This time,
it wasn't Danis.
It was actually him.
If I weren't tied up with
hosting for a shampoo brand,
I would've invited you to Nakhon Sawan.
Huh?
You don't believe me?
Fine. Believe whatever you want!
That's all.
No one believes me
about Grandpa's ghost.
I believe you, though.
Thank you.
Don't come any closer.
Hello, Buddha.
- You're not afraid?
- Stop being scared of me.
I will not do you any harm.
I am here
because I need your help.
You are the only person
who can help me
because you can see me.
Why?
What? How would I know?
Huh...
Maybe because...
you are my grandson.
Our bond lets us connect with each other.
- Bond?
- Mm.
I've never seen you
except in your funeral photo.
Well, now you see me.
Have you heard of Big Ass?
♫Is this what's called "destiny"?♫
♫That led our paths♫
♫To cross and make us meet♫
Pick a song, Grandpa.
Maybe it is because...
the heavens
sent you to help me.
Thank heavens.
Dobby, my beloved grandson!
Wait...
You said, "beloved grandson"?
Didn't you cut ties with my mom?
Go away. Go ask someone else!
I'm not helping you!
I'm going to bed,
so don't bother me!
You are just as stubborn as your mom.
I will not give up that easily.
What are you mumbling about?
I am talking to myself!
Are you really asleep?
Pretending to be asleep, huh?
It is so obvious.
Go learn how to act.
I know you are not asleep.
Stop pretending.
Bang! Bang!
- Bang! Bang!
- Hey!
Bang! Bang!
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Everybody!!
Put your hands up, hands up in the air!
In the air, put your hands up!
Our shampoo...
You did not
sleep well last night, huh, Dobby?
Research...
shows that
the natural essence
is good for your hair health...
Sell these rattle-rattle drums!
- It helps your hair grow nicely.
- Here are the rattle-rattle drums!
Rattle-rattle drums!
It makes your hair roots
go rattle-rattle.
Um, I meant like...
It makes your rattle-rattle hair roots
go all swish-swish strong!
You are witty. Well done.
Yes.
A great shampoo like this
would never have been made
without Mr. Chanint Panthong's
sharp vision.
Our talented executive has
personally tested this product
and seen the results, yes?
Yes.
Black Shell shampoo is why
his hair is thick, black, and strong.
I kind of want to give him a backhand
to see if his hair roots
are actually strong.
Grandpa, don't!
I apologize.
Mr. Chanint, I'm so sorry.
Not that!
Where is it?
I'm sorry, Mr. Chanint.
[The D Dorm]
Now that you've ruined my life,
are you satisfied, Grandpa?
All the organizers canceled my gigs.
You don't believe me?
Look!
[Dobby, you're banned for good]
[The agencies are all banning you]
[If you're banned,
how are you gonna make a living?]
I am sorry. I did not mean to.
Well, I did it on purpose,
but I did not want it to be this bad.
It all started because of you.
You would not help me.
How about this?
If you help me,
I will reincarnate
and stop bothering you.
You can sell the dorm or
do whatever you want with it.
So what do you need my help with?
Well...
it happened on the day I bit the dust...
There is one watermelon.
Split it left.
Split it right.
Watermelon.
♫Watermelon, watermelon, watermelon♫
♫Big and sweet treat♫
♫Whoever eats...♫
What?
I was doing Tai Chi.
Why did I suddenly sing mor lam?
Who is that?
Why is Gaysorn's photo here?
Gaysorn!
Gaysorn, wait for me!
Where are you running off to, Gaysorn?!
Wait for me!
Gaysorn...
Gaysorn!!
Gaysorn!
Gay...
Was my life not tragic?
Gaysorn was my first love.
That day, we both
tried to run away together on the train,
but my dad caught us.
He then forced me to marry
your grandmother.
After that, I never saw Gaysorn again!
Serves you right.
You hate arranged marriages yourself,
but you still forced my mom into one?
One thing to say to you:
"Serves you right."
You would not understand.
It is very complicated.
Huh?
Complicated.
Complicate...
Complex?
Mm.
The thing is...
you need to find out
who owns Gaysorn's picture.
Then take me to them,
so I can find out more about her.
And I will finally be able to apologize to her,
just once in my life.
Wait, Grandpa. Did you forget?
You're a ghost.
Just disappear and go find her!
Why do you need my help?
I have tried that many times already.
It is no use.
I cannot communicate with anyone.
You are the only person
who can help me with this.
If I help you,
you'll stop bothering me, right?
And you'll let me sell this dorm, right?
What?!
Shaking hands?
Here! Fist bump.
That's how Gen Z does it, Grandpa!
I am not a Gen Z. I am a baby boomer.
Fine, I'm in.
Old people are so hard to understand.
Okay, Grandpa, let's go with that.
Gaysorn...
[We're not moving out,
we love this dorm!!]
If we can't talk this out,
I'll have to rally the tenants to protest!
Mm.
I'm done.
"Please show some compassion
for your poor tenants."
What an...
adorable little protest, sweetheart.
I finished mine as well.
Can I see it?
Here.
"First love is hard to move on,
cause I adore the one I gaze upon.
Since it's my first love,
stepping away would be too much, love."
There are two meanings to it.
The first one
is the love I have for you, Ms. Danis.
Second,
it's the love that the tenants
have for this dorm.
Guard Dum,
just bring the signs to
Auntie Duang and the others.
They're waiting.
- Oh, alright.
- Thank you.
Hey...
- Hey!
- What? Hey!
Hey, Mr. Dobby.
Why didn't you catch her?
Yeah.
Why did I have to?
This isn't a K-drama!
Wow, you're heartless!
Come on, you wrinkled my sleeves.
Hey, wait...
Why did you put up these signs?
What's this?
"Ungrateful grandson."
"We're not leaving."
What? "First love...I love my mom." What?!
Take them all down.
I'm not selling this dorm anymore!
- Huh?!
- Huh?
What? Why did you change your mind?
Well...
my grandpa came to me in a dream
and told me,
"I'm too sinful,
so I can't be reincarnated."
That's why he wants me to keep this dorm.
Let people rent it at a low price
to accumulate merit,
so that he'll be sent to heaven.
And he won't have to burn in hell.
It's too painful.
He did a lot of evil, that sort of thing.
Nonsense.
How am I sinful?
Dobby, when did I get into your dreams?!
But on one condition:
as long as I'm here,
no one can move out
without my permission.
Why this condition?
Huh?
It's none of your business!
If you don't want me to sell this dorm,
just do as I say.
It's that simple.
Hey, put them all down.
"First love is hard to move...
Oh, what the heck?"
What sin did I commit?
How am I sinful?!
Dobby!
Talk to me. How am I sinful?!
It's alright, Ms. Danis,
at least he's not going to
sell this dorm.
If we follow his rules,
everything should be fine.
I still can't trust him.
There's gotta be some reason behind this.
I don't know...
Perhaps the old man Dawin mentioned
is his grandpa?
Hmph...
Was that good enough for you, Grandpa?
Don't forget your promise.
I will not forget.
As soon as I meet Gaysorn,
I will be reborn right away.
I will not bother you ever again.
Deal.
Ugh! Leave it.
It's a deal, Grandpa.
Why are you smiling?
I am happy.
I have not seen Gaysorn in a long time.
If I get to see her again...
it would be nice
to apologize to her at least once
before I go.
Have you ever...
wanted to apologize to Mom like this?
I did not do anything wrong!
Your mom was the one at fault!
It's no use talking to someone like you.
Mommy...
Today, my teacher asked
me to draw a family picture.
Why are there only
three people in our family?
Why don't we have
a Grandpa and Grandma like other families?
Why are you crying, Mommy?
Finally...
I get to meet you,
Dobby.
[Nakhon Sawan, 2004]
Here to see your grandchild or child?
Oh, my grandson.
His name is Dobby.
- Dobby?
- Yeah.
His mother probably likes
'Harry Potter,' huh?
Dobby. What an odd name.
Why didn't she name him "Song" or "Gui"?
They sound prettier.
There.
The boy sitting alone
with a sock on his hand.
So?
He's handsome, just like me, yeah?
I'll take a photo.
Why don't you get closer to take a photo?
It's fine. I can take it from here.
Hey!
Don't peek, Grandpa!
Peek...
When I was younger,
I had a much more defined six-pack.
I want you to be my sidekick
and help me find Grandma Gaysorn.
What do I have to do?
There is only one way.
Hm?
Just get Danis on your side.
Everything will be easier.
Danis hates my guts.
Why would she help me?!
What would you like me
to tell you about your fortune?
I want to know
if the coffee shop owner downstairs
is a good match for me.
His shop is about to open,
but I've never even seen him.
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find
what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine,
but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely
when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains,
remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things
await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence
that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings
on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm
is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]